Jacob Namhyung Kim

Front End Developer

Self-motivated developer adds high level of experience over 1 year collaborating and working with team on multiple web and mobile projects. Passionate, hardworking coder with penchant for developing customized interfaces that factor in unique demands for design and accessibility. Focused on creating clean, robust code with exceptional security. Ready to help the team achieve company goals!

Linkedin / everywherejacobkim | Github / everywherejacobkim

Contact

Address

Burnaby, BC

Phone

1-236-838-5758

E-mail

everywherejacobkim@gmail.com

Skills

Javascript

React.js

Next.js

Node.js

React Native

MongoDB

GraphQL

REST API

Headless CMS

Languages

English - Fluent

Korean - Fluent

Diploma in Korean English Interpretation & Translation

Work History

2022-08 -Current

Freelance Developer

Freelancer, Burnaby, BC

- Built from multi page websites to e-commerce platforms with payment gateways.
- Updated old code bases to modern development standards, improving functionality.

2021-08 -2022-12

Brand Associate

Gap Inc., Burnaby, BC

- Assisted with development and implementation of organization brand strategy.
- Engaged with customers to build rapport and loyalty.

2015-01 -2020-12

Program Coordinator / Technical Administrative Assistant

Consulate general of the republic of Korea, Seattle, WA, USA

- Organized and managed cultural and educational programs from conception through successful execution.
- Analyzed website traffic and developed content to meet needs and interests of public website visitors.

Projects

- Handy Chef | Mobile App | React native | MERN | Crossplatform mobile app which connects independent chefs with clients to bring a private restaurant experience to the clients' homes at an affordable rate (www.handychef.ca)
- Pomodee | Web App | React.js | MERN | Fun-and-networkdriven timer app based on pomodoro technique which connects with others to collaborate in real-time study & work sessions (pomodee.com)
- My Travel Story | Web App | Next.js | GraphQL | Travel diary web app that allows users to publish travel memories and interact with other users

Education

2021-05 -2022-12 Post-Degree Diploma: Web And Mobile App Design And Development

Langara College - Vancouver, BC

Bachelor of Science: Educational Technology

Hanyang University - Seoul, South Korea